<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="18"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Humans’ Team
               H      u       m          a      n         s    ’         T    e     a     m










                                                      VS VS









                                                                         T

                                                                ’
                                                                             e

                                                                                        m
                                                                                   a
                                                           s
                                  i
                          n
                   A
                                       m
                                                      l
                   Animals’ Team
                                                 a]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Introduction












       This book is a special creation by Mewen Eechout, a talented Year 7 student who

         poured his creativity into both writing and illustrating this story. Covering the


         themes of Living Things and Sport Aim, Mewen's work showcases not only his


                            imagination but also his dedication to storytelling.

         This book is the result of a class competition I organized to inspire students to


        express themselves through stories. Mewen's outstanding effort earned him the


           winning title, and as his teacher, I wanted to celebrate his achievement in a

             meaningful way. That's why I created this ebook—to keep him engaged,


                      motivated, and encouraged to explore his creativity further.


          This book is dedicated to young readers, proving that great stories can come

        from anyone, at any age. Mewen's work is not just a story; it is a piece of art,


                                       filled with passion and originality.





                Enjoy the journey through the pages of this wonderful creation!





                                                Sarra Ben Amara


                                                  (Main Teacher)]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Four friends named Mewen, Ibrahim, Ahmed and Taher are lost in the jungle.


        Mewen wants to go home. But the Jungle looks like a giant maze!

        So the friends split into two teams:


        team 1: Mewen + Ibrahim.

        team 2: Ahmed, Taher.


        One team goes to the right, the other team to the left.








                                 Ibrahim























                                                                                                      Taher
        Mewen






















                                                                          Ahmed]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[On the team 1 side .....






             Mewen and Ibrahim are walking quietly, in the forest when suddenly,


             Roooooooooooooaaaaaaar !

             They hear a roar. A leopard is in front of the two friends.






        Leopard : Hello, I'm leopard. I will let you pass only if you win the race.


        Mewen : What race.?





        Leopard : The race you have to do Vs me!




        Ibrahim : Ok, let's do this!




        Mewen : We must be careful Ibrahim. The leopard


        is reputed to be the fasest animal on earth !




        Ibrahim : Don't worry! We will win if we do


        \teamwork




        Leopard : 3, 2, 1 Gooooooo....]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[The Leopard was very fast for Ibrahim. But Mewen and Ibrahim prepared

          a plan before the start of the race. The leopard was running so fast that


          they could hardly see its legs move.





          Mewen : Now Ibrahim !!




          Suddenly, Ibrahim went on Mewen's back to jump very high.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[Yeah ! I won .... We




                Wooooooooon !!!!                    Yeah... You did... Good!

























































                                               You're free to go]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Team 2 Adventure ....














             Taher and Ahmed were walking quietly in the forest ( like Mewen and


             Ibrahim). Then a snake came and proposed to Taher and Ahmed to go on



             a football match, so they can leave ....]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Ahmed: A snake playing football ? hahahahahaha...



        Taher & Snake ( at the same moment ) : I don't understand what's


        funny about this ?


        Ahmed : You are a snake, you don't have legs to play !






























































      Snake : I play with my tail...Huh let's play !]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[The football match started. The


         snake was a very good player.






        Snake: The first one who scores a

        goal, wins the match !





        While playing Ahmed was about to kick


        the ball to score, but suddenly the

        snake just wrapped its tail around the


        ball...


        Ahmed : You are cheating !




        Snake: No ... No ...!!!




        The snake was in front of Ahmed's


        cage. He threw the ball but the boy


        caught it well ...





        Few minutes later, Ahmed had


        his chance to score... and that's how he

        made it out ...]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Taher was fighting a monkey in a volleyball match.


        Like the snake the monkey was using his tail to kick and hold the ball.





        the monkey. was better in defense than in attack....











        8 minutes later, Taher won the match,


        when he scored over the monkey.]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Back to team 1....







        Mewen & ibrahim continued walking and then...



           a Big Big gorilla king was there with his boxing gloves.




        Gorilla King : Hey, little tiny kids ! Where are


        you going like this ?


        If you want to go, then you have to fight me!

         If you win both can pass ... But If I win .........




















                       Mewen: Okay ! Let's do this !]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[The gorilla was very strong but Mewen hit him twice on his legs and the

        gorilla fell on the ground.




        Gorilla King : Fiiiiine ! Enough You win ... You can go ....




        Mewen & Ibrahim : Okay , Bye !




           30 minutes later, the boys met up and went home.




        In the evening they told their family everything, about the animals they


        met, the matches they had, the fun and the stress they went through ...











                                          The End]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Now it;s your turn,




                                                   Do you think you'll




                                                   win? Click me and




                                                             let's see]]></page></pages></Search>